Our national tragedy. Their personal suffering. His impossible task.
Worth is a history, drama film directed by Sara Colangelo.
Kenneth Feinberg, a powerful D.C.
lawyer appointed Special Master of the 9/11 Fund, fights off the cynicism, bureaucracy, and politics
associated with administering government funds and, in doing so, discovers what life is worth.
Kenneth Feinberg, played by Michael Keaton.
Camille Biros, played by Amy Ryan.
Charles Wolf, played by Stanley Tucci.
Lee Quinn, played by Tate Donovan.
Priya Khundi, played by Shunori Ramanathan.
Dede Feinberg, played by Talia Balsam.
Worth is a 2020 American biographical film written and co-produced
by Max Borenstein and directed by Sara Colangelo.
Based on the memoir by lawyer Kenneth Feinberg, the film depicts Feinberg's
handling of the September 11th Victim Compensation Fund.
It stars Michael Keaton, Stanley Tucci, Amy Ryan, Tate
Donovan, Talia Balsam, and Laura Benanti.
The film premiered at 2020 Sundance Film Festival on January 24, 2020, where
it was acquired by Netflix and Higher Ground Productions.
The film was given a limited theatrical release in the United States on August 27,
2021, followed by a streaming release on Netflix on September 3
The film explores themes of based on true story, 9/11, world trade center.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.